<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CV Builder</string>
    <string name="forgot"><a href="#">Forgot password?</a></string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="home">Hello home fragment</string>
    <string name="about">Hello about fragment</string>
    <string name="contact">Hello contact fragment</string>
    <string name="experience">Experience</string>
    <string name="name">Yohanns Nigatu</string>
    <string name="position">Software Engineer</string>
    <string name="career_note">
        Talented software developer with 4 years of experience and a strong education in all aspects of full stack
application development. History of implementing, deploying, testing, and supporting successful
applications and embedded systems with high accuracy, maintainability, and performance in the financial
and healthcare domain.
    </string>

    <string name="about_me">
        Talented software developer with extensive hands-on experience and strong educational background in all aspects of full-stack application development. History of implementing, deploying, testing, and supporting successful financial applications and embedded systems with high accuracy, maintainability, and performance. As technologies are changing on a daily basis, I\'m always motivated to learn and adapt to new skills.
    </string>
    <string name="work_experience">
        <b>Languages:</b> Java\n
<b>Web:</b> HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, WordPress, AJAX, jQuery, Bootstrap\n
        <b>Web Services:</b> REST\n
<b>Web/App Servers:</b> XAMPP, Tomcat\n
        <b>Frameworks:</b> NodeJS, ExpressJS, Spring Boot, ReactJS, AngularJS, Angular, Hibernate\n
        <b>Databases:</b> MySQL, MS SQL, MongoDB, Oracle\n
<b>Design Patterns:</b> Singleton, Factory, Template\n
<b>SDLC:</b> Agile-Scrum, Extreme Programming(XP)\n
<b>Tools:</b> NetBeans, Eclipse, IntelliJ, VS Code, Visual Studio, Trello, MS Visio, Sublime Text, Maven, Git,
JUnit, Selenium\n
        <b>Platforms:</b> Windows, Linux
    </string>
    <string name="projects">
        <b>MEAN Travelers Guide, MIU (2021):</b> Individually designed and developed a MEAN application which
provides detailed tourism guides for many countries. Technologies Used: NodeJS, ExpressJS,
MongoDB, AngularJS, Bootstrap, CSS, HTML, Visual Studio Code, Postman, Git\n
        <b>Web Store, MIU (2021):</b> Developed an online e-commerce system where employees may manage
product listings and customers have a smooth shopping experience. Technologies Used: Spring Boot,
JUnit, MongoDB, React, Bootstrap, CSS, Visual Studio Code, IntelliJ, Postman, Selenium, Git
    </string>

    <string name="miu">Maharishi International University</string>
    <string name="msc_major">Master of Computer Science</string>
    <string name="aait">Addis Ababa Institute of Technology</string>
    <string name="bsc_major">Electrical and Computer engineering (Computer) Bsc.</string>

    <string name="devOps_certification">DevOps engineer Certification (2021)</string>
    <string name="spring_cloud_certification">Spring cloud (2022)</string>
    <string name="aws_certification">Amazon web services AWS (2022)</string>

    <string name="cvs">CVS Health</string>
    <string name="apple">Apple Inc</string>
    <string name="cvs_duration_location">Sep 2021 - Present (IL,USA)</string>
    <string name="apple_duration_location">Jan 2021 - Sep 2021 (CA,USA)</string>
    <string name="cvs_responsibility">
        Met all project specifications and requirements for project development.\n
• Designed and developed server-side of recommendation service using Spring Boot \n
• Responsible for developing the code, involved in Agile Extreme programming practices like
Scrum, Pair Programming, TDD, Continuous Integration.\n
• Involved in design and development of UI component, using frameworks Angular, JavaScript,
HTML5, CSS3.\n
• Tested, troubleshot, and deployed finalized applications.\n
• Provided support for errors and technical issues.\n
    </string>
    <string name="apple_responsibility">
Developed new applications and modified existing systems for POS machines.\n
• Met all project specifications and requirements for project development.\n
• Designed aesthetic user interfaces and implemented functional algorithms.\n
• Tested, troubleshot, and deployed finalized applications.\n
• Customized existing applications to meet new business needs.\n
• Provided support for errors and technical issues in both hardware and software.\n
• Trained client employees and end-users on new versions and features.\n
    </string>

    <string name="phone_number">571-397-8386</string>
    <string name="email_address">ynigatu@miu.edu</string>
    <string name="linkedin">Yohanns Nigatu</string>
    <string name="linkedin_id">https://www.linkedin.com/in/yohanns-nigatu/</string>
    <string name="github_id">https://github.com/jocha50</string>
    <string name="github">\@JoCha50</string>






</resources>
